Thank you for watching!
Thank you so much for everything!
Hello! This time we have with us Ebata Kisaki of JuiceJuice and
and Yoferno from Tsubaki Factory.
This time, I'll be talking with these two.
Please bear with me until the end.
Yes, we are the two trainees who joined the group in the same year.
What is the perfect word to describe us two?
I was wondering what would be the perfect word to describe the two of us.
I think it would be something like "rivals".
Rivalry is a perfect word for us.
We have always been in friendly competition since we were trainees.
I think "rival" is the most suitable word.
JuiceJuice is going to perform the final show of their tour at Nippon Budokan today.
The tour finale was held at Nippon Budokan today.
When I look back on this tour, the first thing that comes to mind is
For me personally
I think that my voice has become much easier to produce.
I think that my voice volume has
I'm happy to be able to feel that my voice volume has improved a little.
Also, in terms of the group as a whole
There was a lot of stirring in this fall tour.
Various members are doing it for various songs, so I feel like we are united as one with fans.
I felt like I was united with the fans and had a lot of fun.
I remember that it was a lot of fun.
Yes, Tsubaki Factory held the tour final at Nippon Budokan just a month ago.
Tsubaki Factory held the final show of the tour at Nippon Budokan just a month ago.
Um...
Mr. Yamagishi and
and Mr. Kishimoto graduated
and Mr. Kishimoto graduated and started a new organization.
I think I have to change myself.
I need to change the way I deal with Tsubaki.
How do you say?
These two
Mr. Yamagishi and Mr. Kishimoto
They are great performers in dancing and singing.
even after they are gone and the new organization is formed.
I'd like them
I would like to improve my performance more so that I can fill the hole of
I would like to polish my performance even more so that I can fill in the gaps left by the other two.
And from January 2nd next year
Hello Project 2024 Winter
3 of us will start!
Yes, Tsubaki Factory will be in Team A
Juice Juice will be on Team B.
Yes, that's right.
We haven't done this "3 of us" thing very often.
We've never done it before.
We are in a different team.
I'm hoping to absorb a lot of inspiration from the members of the other group.
I hope to absorb a lot from them and do my best.
How about you, Ume?
What about you, Ume-chan?
For example, Morning Musume or
Yonge-san, for example.
I'm looking forward to playing those songs that we don't usually play.
I'm sure I'll be able to do it.
I want to do my best.
I'll do my best.
Now, please watch this video.
Here you go.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
I'll be going.
Please.
Oh no.
Thank you for your patience.
I think we had a great performance yesterday, so keep it up.
Let's keep it up. Let's make it up as we go along.
Let's do our best!
Shine!
I'm off!
Please do!
Please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
Don't worry, you can do it Don't be afraid
I'm for you
I'm just a clumsy girl
I'll love you straight
I'm for you, I'm for you, I'm for you
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Love is strange, it's strong
I'm not me, I'm here
I want to make you cry
♪ I'll show you the power of love
You're so strange, you're just innocent
That's what's so great about you
Ah, I've never done anything like this before
I want you to know what love looks like
Everybody loves you so much
And you'll fall in love with him
You're so charming, you're so charming
A little more. Sometimes it's not enough.
But for now, you're the one that's gonna change the world
I pray that you'll change it
Please change it into a wonderful planet
I love you
Don't give up, for example, your hands
Don't give up
I love you
Infinite elopement
Though I can't push a little
My unwavering love
I'll protect you
You, my love, are in my position
Don't worry, even if your eyes wander
Don't give up on me
To you, my love, infinite love for you
Though you won't fall a little
My unwavering love for you
I'll protect you
Are you having fun? Watch the rest of the show.
From here, I'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Good luck!
Today, December 6, is Sound Day!
What is your favorite musical sound?
Yes, it's a sound often used in Hello Project songs.
It's the sound of something buzzing.
First overseas solo live performance this year
How do you feel about the experience of performing overseas?
Yes, I was able to unite with everyone through music.
What are you working hardest on right now?
Yes, to make the stage my own through performance.
Relax, dance, and sing!
You often give nicknames to the members.
If you were to give yourself a nickname, what would it be?
Let's see, "Furufuru Furufuru".
What would be the perfect catchphrase for Tabuki Factory's new recruiting system?
Please give us a catchphrase that best fits the new job structure of Tabuki Factory.
Chameleon
Yes, so I got a quick answer.
Personally, I was wondering...
You said that if you were to give yourself a nickname, it would be "Furfurufuru.
Why?
Well, I call everyone by a nickname that is easy to call me.
So I should call myself Furfurufuru to match the atmosphere and the ease of calling me...
I should call you "Furfurufuru" too.
I don't know...
It's easier to call you and I think we'll get along better.
I always focus on being easy to call.
Ease of calling, and, uh, atmosphere and appearance.
I see.
Tabuki Factory's catchphrase, which is now part of the recruitment system
Chameleon
Cameleon
Maybe Cameleon is better.
Because Tsubaki Factory is called Camelia
Oh yeah, yeah, that's what they call it, Cameleon
Cameleon.
Cameleon?
Okay, Cameleon.
Well, you have an image of Tsubaki as a girlish musician, don't you?
Yes.
But recently we've been doing some cool songs with a lot of excitement.
Cameleon means that we can be many different colors.
CAMELEON
Chameleon
Yes, that's right.
Questions for Evata-san after the VTR
Halo! Ste!
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
That one lie is all it takes! Dedee!
Morning Musume。23 す すごいフィーバー!
Now on sale!
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun knows that
Wake up call It's time to wake up Now on ZION
Morning Musume。23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never ending shine Now on ZION
Crossing the red line, I want to get hurt, I want to get hurt
I do, I do, I'm a saver
I just want to be here and tell my heart
My life is open with my mouth
I'm pretty full I'm having so much fun
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry
Life is beautiful
December 13th on ZION
Never ending shine show Sanctuary has finished!
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
I just wanted to say Sanctuary for nothing.
I get it!
I understand!
I don't want Sanctuary to be forgotten.
Sanctuary!
How was it? Today!
We all had so much fun.
We had so much fun.
Walking around.
I felt so close to the audience.
I was having so much fun!
I was smiling the whole time.
I cried at the end.
But I was smiling so much.
I was able to enjoy the show until the end.
That's great!
We did it!
Yes!
I couldn't believe I was standing in Yokohama Arena
I was really nervous.
I thought it would be hard to see the audience's faces
I was so happy to be able to see all the way to the back of the stage.
I'm so glad!
It's true!
Thank you so much!
Next time?
What's next?
What do you think?
This is my first time to perform at Yokohama Arena.
I'm not usually so nervous.
But my heart is racing.
I'm so nervous.
I can't stop laughing.
I mean...
But I was so nervous that my nerves were blown away.
Seeing the faces of the fans
and the colorful lights of the ten lights.
I think it was a really fun concert.
And I think it will be a memory for the rest of my life
I think it will be a memory for the rest of my life.
Thank you very much.
Oh?
Oh, yes.
Um, well...
After Mizuki graduates, as the 10th leader of
I'll be the 10th leader of Morning Musume。 I'm going to be the leader of Morning Musume。
I personally feel that although I am the leader, I am more of a member.
but I have a stronger sense of being a member.
I hope to lead Morning Musume。 I want to lead Morning Musume。
I want to lead Morning Musume。 I would like to make Morning Musume。
I would like to make Morning Musume。
Thank you for your support.
Okay.
Yes, Mizuki? Right?
Mizuki.
Mizuki? Right?
Sorry, sorry.
Erin just turned into a fixture, didn't she?
That's right.
Okay.
How do you feel?
I don't know, I didn't really feel it,
But after it was over, after I threw up, I felt it,
I'm just glad to be back here with you guys, making comments and stuff,
I'm sure.
Yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow.
But I won't be able to see you tomorrow.
That's true.
I'll definitely see you.
I'll see you, but I'll be working with everyone.
But if it's a Christmas event, can I be a guest?
Guest? Guest?
Guest?
Too soon.
No, it's not. But really.
Yes, it is. That's why,
I feel like I'm realizing it more and more and more,
But today's concert itself was a lot of fun,
I was able to make eye contact with many fans,
I don't know.
I was able to make a lot of eye contact with the fans, and I don't know,
There are moments when you make eye contact with the band members while playing a song.
I really enjoyed that part of the concert,
I want to see the DVD.
Wow.
Wow, that's true.
I want to see it.
The Blu-ray?
Yeah. Blu-ray.
Yes, Blu-ray. I really want to see it,
It was a wonderful concert.
Thank you very much.
Hallo! Thank you very much.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Mr. Evatto.
I will do my best.
There are only 25 days left in 2023. Looking back on the past year, tell me about your biggest encounters.
I have made more friends.
JuiceJuice Tense Anniversary Concert Tour JuiceJuice at Budokan was released today, what do you personally want people to see?
The beginning of "Future Smile" is arranged a little longer.
What ability do you want to get now?
The ability to manipulate time.
What hair color would you like to try now?
A high tone blonde-white hair color with a cropped bob.
What would you like to do in 2023?
Decluttering.
Thank you very much.
I was wondering what abilities you would like to have?
The ability to manipulate time.
What is it?
For example, if I can stop or speed up the time when I oversleep, I can sleep in again.
That's for sure.
So I would like to have the ability to manipulate time.
What hair color would you like to try?
How do you know so much about it? How do you know so much about it?
I don't know, I guess I'm not very good at it.
I've always had black hair, so if I were to try it, I'd like to play with high tones at least once.
It looks good on you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it does.
Hello! We will continue after this.
Thank you for your hard work.
Next time, we will bring you the video of Halo! Ste. video will be brought to you.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Look forward to seeing your new video in the next issue.
See you soon.
Thanks for watching.
I like you too much to wonder.
If only there was another me.
I'd be able to protect you even more.
I love you so much that I can't do it anymore
I love you so much, no matter what we do
I don't want to leave you. I want to be close to you.
If I'm too close, I can't see you
You know what they say about people... they're a bunch of stupid moms.
I'm just a tangle of stupid moms
But I don't call them that
If this love is your mama's mama
I'll take it
But this feeling, too...
You're a stupid mama
I'm just a nightmare in your head.
I think, like a philosopher
I can't make it work
Hotter than the sun
More beautiful than the stars
I've tried to love you more
If it were you, I'd be human.
I'm so small
But there is love
There is a love
A love that never ends
Even tens of thousands of years in the future
Shining, sprouting
With this thought
Thank you for watching.
Human beings are so small and insignificant, but we can change the future.
But there is also love, the love of two people, and even tens of thousands of years from now, it's fine to let it sprout.
This feeling
Nanana...
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Play on
You're working too hard, take a break
JuiceJuice's Hisaki Ebata and
Yofu Luno of Tsubaki Factory presents "Halo! Sta.
As I mentioned in the opening
As I mentioned in the opening, we are trainee classmates.
I'd like to introduce an unexpected side of the other that I'm probably the only one who knows.
Now that both of us are back in our sketchbooks, let's make an announcement!
Se-na-no!
rock, paper, scissors!
Pure
Okay, let's start with Luna.
First of all, I think Evata is very pure.
She's usually very caring.
And he's a bit of a naughty boy, but...
But what makes me think she's pure is...
When I was a trainee, I was the first one to join the group.
We were from Kansai, right?
And I was speaking in Kansai dialect.
But when we came to Tokyo, Eva Kisaki came to us.
When I came to Tokyo, Ebata Kisaki told me that I shouldn't use the Kansai dialect.
When I went to Tokyo, she told me that I shouldn't use Kansai dialect.
But at that time, I felt...
What? I felt that she was using Kansai dialect.
At that time, I thought, "What? She's not like that.
She's so pure.
I thought she was so pure and cute.
She probably told me that I shouldn't use the Kansai dialect at that time.
So I thought I should tell Luna-chan about it.
The episode was that even I was speaking in Kansai dialect.
I believed that for a while.
I always told her that she shouldn't use Kansai-ben.
I thought it was very pure that they always kept it together.
And that's why I'm...
Hmmm...
Erno is surprisingly quiet.
Wow!
I don't know how Haruno-chan is when she's with Tsubaki Factory members, but...
I don't know about when Haruno-chan is with the members of Tsubaki Factory, but when it's just the two of us, I think she's often rather quiet.
Rather than talking to each other all the time...
We're more like pamilies.
More like sisters at home.
I get it.
I thought it might be a surprise to you.
That's true.
Yes, well, we went out to eat together before this recording,
And even before this recording, we went out for dinner together, and she was not at all cautious at that time.
In a good way, I mean, I was not cautious at all,
Even in a quiet place, I could relax,
I can relax even in a quiet place, and I can relax even when we are talking a lot,
That's the kind of relationship I want to have with you all the time.
So, the two of you, who are called "everno," will continue to work hard together,
I hope we can continue to work hard and compete with each other in a friendly way.
Hallo! Ste!
Kisaki Ebata of JuiceJuice and Runo Yofu of Tsumaki Factory will be presenting a new series of "Halo! Stay!
It is time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
JuiceJuice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour
JuiceJuice at Budokan is going on sale today.
I'm sure you will be able to see the culmination of everyone's performance,
I'm sure you will be able to see the culmination of everyone's efforts, and I'm sure some of you may feel a little nostalgic,
I hope you will watch it a lot.
JuiceJuice will be performing at the Cho-Idol Fest on December 21 with Ocha-no-Oma.
I hope we can learn a lot from the other idols who will also be there.
Tsumaki Factory will perform at Idol Wave in Tokyo on December 29.
There will be many other idols there as well,
I would like to see a lot of the present that can only be seen at that time.
And Hello Project Year End Party 2023 Goodbye & Hello will be held on December 30 and 31.
On December 31, it will be held simultaneously in Tokyo and Osaka.
JuiceJuice will be in Osaka,
Tsumaki Factory will be in Tokyo and Osaka at the same time.
JuiceJuice will perform in Tokyo. Please come and see them.
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of As will start on January 2 next year.
Tsumaki Factory will perform as Team A and JuiceJuice will perform as Team B.
We are both separate groups, but we will do our best.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will appear more and more.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel,
Please subscribe to our channel.
This time I'm with Kisaki Ebata of JuiceJuice,
and Runo Yofu of Tsumaki Factory.
Good bye.
Mitsubishi! Mitsubishi! Mitsubishi!
Thank you so much for all your calls to Mizuki!
I still can't believe that I am graduating.
I've written a letter and I'd like to tell you how I feel.
Thank you so much!
Today, November 29th, I, Mizuki Fukumura, will graduate from Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
On January 2, 2011, ZUNK gave me the magic words
Since that day, I have been a member of Morning Musume。 I became a member of Morning Musume。
I loved Hello Project so much
I auditioned for the Hello Project just because I loved it so much.
There was a gap between the world I had always dreamed of and the world I wanted to be a part of.
I realized that it takes many times more effort and hard work than I had imagined.
I was sometimes torn between what I loved and what I wanted to do.
There were seniors who gave me words of courage
I was saved a lot by the message of Mr. ZUNK's music
I always had reassuring members next to me
I was able to perform for 3 days with those members.
Concerts every day during Golden Week
Non-stop for 40 minutes
We even survived an outdoor festival in the middle of summer.
I was really happy.
And to our fans
To our fans who gave us great love
We are able to do our activities with smiles on our faces because of your great love.
We will be strong again and again in the future, remembering your words.
Thank you so much!
Applause
I've been running as Morning Musume。 I still can't think about what I will be doing tomorrow.
But finally, my dream of entrusting my dream to my juniors will come true.
Morning Musume。 There are so many wonderful girls in Morning Musume。
The 17th term members have been with the group for six months. They still look anxious during rehearsals, but on stage, they show us their full-fledged faces.
Haru-san and Ako-chan. I hope you will gain more and more experience and become Morning Musume in your own way.
The 16th term. It's only been two years since I joined Morning Musume, but we've become such good friends thanks to Riley.
Riley has brought various possibilities to Morning Musume.
She is the king of Morning Musume's expression. Please keep up the good work.
Mei, who is free-spirited and radiates the power of being loved.
Cute Mei.
Honor, who shows true strength in her cuteness. Kita, who is as washed and beautiful as a lake. The 15th term, with its wonderful three-way singing voice.
The three of them healed me a lot. Too much love came out and all the members became grandmothers.
I am watching over them as they grow and become active with their power.
13th term. Yokota is versatile and absolutely secure.
She is a sweetheart but also a big sister, helping us in many areas.
I'm sure she will continue to naturally support everyone. Thank you so much for your kindness, Yokota.
The 12th term, which we unveiled on this stage nine years ago, all three of them have grown up.
Nonaka with her delicate yet bold singing voice, Maria with her home-run effort,
Akanetin, who conveys full of love, though a bit heavy on love.
I believe that their unwavering hearts will make Morning Musume。 I believe that their unwavering hearts will make Morning Musume。
Oda!
It's unique, but everything is a mass of love. I hope you will continue to love music and rhythm like Oda,
I hope you will continue to love music, rhythm, and Morning Musume。 I hope you will continue to love music, rhythm, and Morning Musume。 Thank you for always leading us with your songs.
Ayumi is the only member of Haropro who is the same age as me. I have a lot of fond memories of Ayumi.
I hope you will continue to shine with your competitive spirit, spirit, and enthusiasm, and make the best use of your strengths.
And Eripon, my classmate. Thank you for supporting me for 13 years.
Thank you for supporting me.
The place where you have strong beliefs.
I have seen how you are loved by many people.
Eripon will be fine.
I know you will be a part of the future of Morning Musume。 Please take care of Morning Musume。
I'll keep you in my thoughts.
I'm sure Morning Musume。 will never leave my mind.
It is such an irreplaceable existence
I met my friends
on this stage of Yokohama Arena.
Oritoide
The girl who was incredibly happy that day
is the happiest person in the world today.
I'm so happy to see such a beautiful deep pink scenery
I'm so happy
Thank you very much.
Once again
It's been 15 years since I started as a member of Halo Pro Egg, and 13 years as a member of Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
Thank you so much for meeting me and finding me.
I am sure that no matter how many years pass, I will remember today and think thank you for that time.
You will always be special to me.
Thank you so much.
Morning Musume。 Mizuki Fukumura.
Applause
Thank you for watching.
I'm all alone on a dreary night
I'm the only one who's lonely.
I got a silly and funny e-mail.
I don't know why I can't stop crying. Oh, thank you.
I know me better than anyone.
I know me better than anyone else, so I have to trust you more than anyone else
Lyrics, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Life is wonderful
This is what it's like to meet someone
Meet someone, fall in love
It's wonderful
In the universe
You can have a rose or a cry
Bluffing with someone.
Some days I'm afraid to talk about it
Yeah, but I'm brave enough to tell you.
About me
Yes, there will be sunny days
Yeah, and then it's gonna rain
Someday it'll all make sense
Life's so great, you know? It's always the same
We'll find something that's the same as the road we're on
♪ It's great to find someone
I'm gonna find someone I'm gonna meet
Wow, wow, wow, wow Yeah
Sunny day
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Wh
me
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Life goes on
Wonderful, you know, someone to meet
Let's meet someone. Now's the day I came
In the most wonderful outfits.
I'm missing, I'm missing, I'm missing.
Life is great.
Even if it's the same road, let's find something new.
Let's find something new
Let it be the way we meet
But I want to keep a smile on my face
Yeah
For the one I love
Clap your hands
Okay, I'm ready.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
It's over.
It's down. I'm down.
I've got tissues.
It's wrapped around your finger.
How do you feel? How do you feel now?
It's gone. It's gone. It's gone.
That's great, guys.
Around the perimeter.
Were you crying?
Yeah, they were crying.
You were crying so loud.
I tried to scream as hard as I could.
But I was losing my voice.
I was losing to the fans.
But...
No regrets.
I had a great time.
Thank you so much.
bowing to you
Thank you very much
I, Mizuki Fukumura
November 29th
Yokohama Arena
After the graduation performance
I will be leaving Morning Musume。 and Hello Project
Morning Musume and Hello Project.
Hello Project Egg
For the first time
when
I was a member of
15 years
since I was a little girl.
Hello! I've been with the pros
I have lived
Hello!
I've lived
Such a life
What's going to happen now?
I can't imagine.
Today's show was...
I had a lot of fun.
I could finally realize that I'm going to graduate.
I'm going to take some time off now.
I will make time to face myself again
And I will do my best to improve my skills and come back to you.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Please look forward to the future of Morning Musume。 Please look forward to the future of Morning Musume。
Thank you very much.
This is Mizuki Fukumura.
Thank you for watching!